Hafiz Elfia Wedo Putra

hafizelfiawedoputra@outlook.com | linkedin.com/in/hafizewp | github.com/hafizewp22

SUMMARY

Having experience in web development at my internship company and I am interested in technology. I am also a hard worker, have integrity, responsibility and work in a team. Really like and interesting coding such as UI/UX, websites and data analysis to create attractive programs.

EDUCATION

BINA NUSANTARA UNIVERSITY

Jakarta, Indonesia

Bachelor of Computing in Computer Science

2019 - Present

Streaming: Database Technology

GPA: 3.33 / 4.0

- Thesis: Design Of Web-Based Learning Media To Improve Learning Systems In Poris Indah Tangerang High School.
- Participated in INC 2020 in a team named GoGainer, and placed 70th ranking of 700 teams National level.
- Winner of Designing UI/UX with Figma Competition (3rd place on campus level).
- Conducting research on Augmented Reality for Human Digestive Anatomy Biology Learning (June 2021) [View]
- Creating a website-based application about an online store using Laravel 8.0. [View]
- Create a website for information about COVID-19 data in Indonesia. [View]
- Data analysis on information about COVID-19 Vaccination in Indonesia. [View]

EXPERIENCE

PT. TELKOM INDONESIA

Jakarta, Indonesia

Web Developer – Internship

March 2022 – Present

- Successfully updated the SIIS, MySIISTA and IBAM websites using the ReactJs programming language to add new pages and features to the map, namely GIS (Geographic Information System) and React Leaflet.
- Update API data input from Arcgis on the SIIS 4.0 website and API data input on the IBAM website page.
- Participate in training to create a Usecase Bootcamp application quiz lesson.

BINA NUSANTARA UNIVERSITY

Tangerang, Indonesia

Student Mentor

October 2021 – February 2022

 The Community Care for Friends at BINUS University which provides the task of helping friends who have special attention and high concern for disability issues and special needs on campus.

BINA NUSANTARA COMPUTER CLUB

Tangerang, Indonesia

Organization - Learning and Training Staff

August 2020 - February 2022

- Establish curriculum and class materials and schedules for classes and teaching.
- Become an event committee in organizations related to Information Technology.
- Create and do attendance for each LnT class.

Organization - Learning and Teaching Division Activist

July 2019 – October 2022

- MC training and talk.
- Student Leadership and Management Exercises (LKMM).
- Training and learning to create Website design (HTML & CSS).

ADDITIONAL

Hard Skill:

HTML5, CSS, PHP, Javascript, Java, Laravel, ReactJS, Figma (Software), MySQL/SQL, Database Design, Data Analysis, Git

Soft Skill:

Teamwork, Time Management, Leadership

Language:

Fluent in Indonesia, Elementary Proficiency in English

Certifications & Training:

Web Development Path (Node.js), HTML Course (Sololearn), Introduction to HTML5 (University of Michigan), Problem Solving Basic (HackerRank), Java Basic (HackerRank), SQL Basic (HackerRank), Database Design and Programming with SQL (Training - Oracle FGA 2021), React Udemy, Introduction to Back-End Development (Meta), React Basic (HackerRank)

Project:

Clothing Store Cashier Application in Web (2018), Website Based Online Store "BukaWarung" (2022), Website Based Online Store "JH Furniture" (2022)